Why you act like you've never blogged
before in your life?
>> Welcome to my blog in New York City. My
sister's over
in my apartment, obviously, cuz we're in
my apartment. And we're going to be
>> We're going vintage shopping.
>> We're going to go vintage shopping.
>> I'm so excited. I want a Fendi bag so
bad.
>> I love you guys.
>> It was raining just like 2 minutes ago,
and it stopped. So, I think that's a
sign.
>> I kind [clears throat] of wish I wore
different pants, actually, but
this will do. We're just going to be out
for this vintage shop.
And yeah.
I'll see if I get anything. I don't
really know if I want anything, to be
honest.
But
we shall see. Oh my god, I don't even
have my phone.
>> So excited. I really hope there's a bag
for me, and if not, maybe some
sunglasses, cuz I really want some cool
sunnies. So
>> Okay, I kind of want to get these
glasses
tightened a little bit on the side.
But I love how big it is, cuz it makes
my face look small.
>> It's looking huge.
>> Right now, we're going to group chat
with our show producer. As you guys
know, we're going We're hosting a show
live in New York City, and we're having
weekly meetings and planning what to do.
I feel like we haven't really talked
about the behind the scenes about it,
but we are going to be doing something
really exciting. It's not just going to
be like we're not just going to be
sitting and talking on stage. We're
going to make it like really really
interactive.
>> It's going to be like a YouTube video
IRL.
>> Yeah. So, that I think
>> It's going to be so fun, guys. I'm
really excited.
>> [screaming and crying]
>> Of course, when I have a picture I look
good in, this is making the ugliest
face [clears throat] in the back.
Like definition. No, I didn't catch you
did it on purpose.
>> Comment down below if I should change up
my pic like the frames here.
I'm starting to get sick of it.
What do you What do you think?
Should I do something different?
Like should I just like get rid of it
and
get rid of it?
Like I'd have a white background.
>> I don't know.
>> And also
my Lego collection up here.
I'm also starting to get sick of this.
So, kind of want to get rid of this.
>> change it to?
>> I don't know, but do something
different.
What are you doing?
Immediately immediately regretting my
outfit
outfit choice right now.
It's so hot.
>> It is.
>> Yeah, it's 90° outside and I'm wearing
long sleeve. Both top and bottom.
>> Why did you do that?
>> I don't know.
You know what, guys?
We'll be back. We'll be back home so I
can change.
It's started to rain again.
Oh. And it just stopped.
>> [laughter]
>> It's so weird.
I think something's wrong with my
fingers.
My ring got way bigger on me.
>> Let me try this.
It doesn't fit any of my fingers.
>> Try your ring one.
Does it fit your ring? What about your
pointer?
>> No, just my rings.
>> What? It's so big on me.
>> Well, it's cuz your fingers are like so
bony. It's literally just like
Like
>> We're here, guys. I'm so hungry.
>> I know.
>> Emily has been dying to visit this
vintage shop in New York.
>> It's called Rebag London.
>> Hello.
>> Hi.
>> Hi. Hello.
>> Hi. Good.
Ooh.
>> What style of bag were you wanting?
>> This style?
Are you serious?
Is this cute or not?
>> Yeah.
>> What do you think?
>> It's cute.
It feels like caviar, right?
>> Yeah.
>> There's so many cute stuff here.
Erica has that, but the bigger the
bigger version.
>> Bigger version.
>> Um.
That one's cute, too.
That's cute.
Or like this. This is so cute. It's a
little scratchy.
I thought you were talking to me.
>> [laughter]
>> Imagine.
>> Ooh, that one's really cute.
>> That's so fun.
>> [music]
>> Oh, that's so cute.
>> But I love the cheetah print. [music]
>> I like this.
>> [music]
>> Erica, I mean Emily, Emily got it back.
>> So happy.
>> Wait, this tote bag is so cute.
>> Thank you.
>> So freaking cute.
>> Oh my god, I want this one. I want this
one.
>> Yeah.
>> I call it. [music]
>> I call it Noah.
Thank you. How are you feeling about
your purchase?
>> I am so happy, guys. This is all I
wanted. I didn't end up getting a Fendi
bag like I wanted, but I think this bag
is just as cute as the Fendi bag that I
did want. So, let me Should I show them?
>> You can do it like at home.
>> Did you tell them what you got?
>> I got
>> We got the Oishii Berry Matcha from
Matcha Bowl, and I only just drank the
berries just now. I thought
>> Guys, you didn't see if there was a
mango a mango
>> flavor.
>> I know. We saw We saw a different drink
that looked 10 times better.
And then I was like,
"Where was that?
Why did I not see that?"
Anyways, matcha cuz I was literally I'm
not even kidding when we were vintage
shopping, my eyes were like falling
asleep. [laughter]
I was looking at the bags and I'm like,
"I think it's cute."
>> [laughter]
>> So,
a little pick-me-up before dinner cuz we
have dinner in 2 hours, but we want to
go home back home
to like change, freshen up. I want to
change my outfit so bad right now. Like
I
if I come out with like
not the most perfect outfit,
I need to go back home and change.
>> and go back home.
>> I need to go back home.
>> It's okay.
>> [laughter]
>> No, don't worry. Don't worry.
Okay, we're back home. And let me show
you guys the City bag that I PURCHASED
TODAY.
>> [screaming]
>> EMILY'S
second
second designer bag.
>> Designer purchase.
>> This is my first vintage purchase
though. I I have never owned a vintage
bag before. Here she is.
So cute. Oh my gosh. [screaming]
I got the smaller city bag cuz I feel
like this is more cash.
>> So cute and I love the color green.
>> Yeah. Erica has She has this in the
bright color green in the in the very
big version.
So cute.
>> Oh, my lovely bag.
>> cute.
>> Guys, I
just like want to freaking
>> I got this at such a good price and I'm
so happy with it and next time I go
there I'm going to get the Gucci bag.
Cuz the Gucci bag was also so freaking
cute.
>> Kai's the best dog ever. Genuinely, like
I
You're the sweetest doggy [snorts]
>> Yeah.
Anyone can ask for.
Yes, that's right.
That is right, honey.
Hey.
>> Hey guys.
We changed.
>> Let me give you a fit check. So, this
dress This dress is from For Love &
Lemons. Same shoes from before and
Evelyn's Dior bag.
>> I'm wearing this tank top from For Love
& Lemons. The The skirt is from Doen
and my uh kitten heels from Jimmy Choos.
Bag is from The Row.
And
that's all I'm wearing. My apartment is
so messy right now, so it's like really
embarrassing, honestly. I'm so hungry.
Um we're getting dinner pretty early
today. Sleepover with the
I'm excited.
>> Hey guys, we're at
the restaurant.
>> I'm actually disappointed.
>> And this man peer pressured me to buy
buy a whole bottle of white wine.
>> It's cuz I was going to my I was going
to my second half.
>> No, but you had your own.
>> We took so many pictures.
>> I don't know what you're talking about.
Anyways guys,
we're dying from the heat cuz it's so
hot.
And I'm I don't know what to do with
this wine. Like we have
I didn't hear him.
I accidentally agreed to a bottle of
wine and I did not
This genuinely looks like the best thing
ever.
Wait, try this.
You're going to die at this.
Isn't it so good?
Holy
There's lobster in it.
Shut up. You were right.
It's been so good.
Good morning. It's the next day.
Yesterday was so much fun. I ate a lot
of food with Emily and today's a new
day. Emily and I want to do something
really fun. We have the whole Saturday
together
and I we want to explore a East Side. We
might just do like a whole bunch of girl
activities. So
It's going to be a fun day. I'm about to
get ready for the day, obviously, and I
just want to show you guys my routine.
My summer New York routine because it is
so hot here. It is hot, humid,
disgusting, hot, sunny, like
So, this is what I do to make sure my
makeup and everything keeps intact.
And how I survive this hot summer
weather. I already did my basic skin
care, but it's been like an hour since I
did it. So, I'm going to go in with my
Haruharu WONDER Black Rice Probiotic
Barrier 2% NAD Serum Mist. So, this is
not like the typical
serum mist. And I also put this like
on my chest and pretty much on
my back as well.
This is not like a typical face mist.
This specific one protects your skin
barrier. It has a super water-like
texture and runs like toner. It's not
like a It's almost like a serum level
barrier care with no stickiness, no
heaviness. And I like to use this before
my makeup, after my makeup, and then
after like at the end of the day after
I've been in the sun for so long. This
helps calm down my skin. So, I really
highly recommend.
I think it's really popular in Korea.
So, I got a recommendation for that.
Okay. And then after, I'm going to go in
with my sunscreen. I'm using the I'm
From Centella Calming Daily Sun Water.
Guys, if you know me, I hate sunscreen.
Um it's literally the worst. I hate how
it feels on my skin.
But this is in like a
toner-like Ooh. Oh my god, I just
spilled it. This is like a toner-like
texture.
It's like actually the best way to apply
sunscreen. Like I actually love this
so much. The way it feels on my skin,
it's not sticky, it's not gross feeling.
I I up putting on way more sunscreen to
protect my skin. This is such a hack. I
don't know why more sunscreen brands do
this, this toner effect. It has no white
cast, no stickiness, no heaviness, no
oiliness, which is so important for me,
especially if you're wearing it under
your makeup. My makeup also applies very
nicely over. As you guys know, I have
rosacea, so I really need sunscreen to
protect my skin from breaking out. And
this sunscreen does exactly that, so.
So, for my face, that's pretty much it.
Another thing I want to show you guys
that I do in the summer time in New
York,
Medicube Kojic Acid Turmeric Body Peel
Shot. I don't know if I pronounced that
right at all, but I discovered this when
I was in Coachella
back in April. I started using it
because
during like when it gets really hot and
humid, I get like
I don't know, my skin is not perfect, so
I have like back
dark spots from like pimples or
whatever, so I use this on my back.
Sometimes like on my armpit, my knees
and all and all that stuff, and it helps
brighten it up, exfoliate, and lighten
up all the dark spots. So, I just
thought I should let you guys know about
this product cuz it is literally the
best. All you do is Oh, here, I'll show
you.
It's basically like a peeler and
it exfoliates your skin like so.
It is so satisfying, too.
And I just rub it in.
It's formulated with BHA, PHA, and LHA
for visible skin concerns.
And then wash it all off.
But yeah, it's really easy to use, and I
find it to be very effective. I got all
of these products from YesStyle,
obviously that's like the most iconic
website that you get Korean products
from. They have all of like the
trendiest K-beauty products there, like
all the trendiest and the newest
products. So, definitely check that out.
I'll also link all of the products that
I'm using in this video in my
description box if you guys
want to take a look and buy something
for yourself. I'm going to fast forward
my makeup and
meet you guys when I'm looking better.
I'm not sure why this is so zoomed out.
This is so zoomed out. I don't know if I
can zoom it.
Toodles.
Yay.
Oh my goodness. Yes, you are. You're so
excited.
>> We're here at Joe and the Juice. I might
get Naya.
>> Okay.
>> I'm going to go get Naya.
>> We'll meet at Joe and the Juice.
>> Okay.
>> Hi. Can I [music] do a spicy tuna
sandwich
and
a Miami Glow large smoothie?
So, I have face tracking on and I don't
know if I like it or not.
It's like following me.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Hi China.
Ty was like looking for you the whole
time. Yeah, her head was like
Oh, I'm right here.
I'm right here.
>> All right.
>> Guys, look at her fire my bowl up.
I love Naya, though.
What did you get?
>> I got a spicy tuna sandwich.
>> Sandwich?
>> With a large Miami Glow smoothie.
>> First bite.
I got my Miami Glow
smoothie.
Try in the back. It's actually so funny.
Just finished eating our food, and now
Emily wants to stop by Brandy to see if
there's anything to buy here.
>> Look at their big backpacks on the
shelves.
>> Ooh, let's go in. Let's go in.
>> It's giving like evening prom dress.
>> Like with my outfit?
We came back home. I slept for like an
hour. I got woken up to Emily almost
burning my house on fire. [laughter]
>> She Bro, I tried. I put the Eggo in. I
tried making one singular Eggo, okay?
One chocolate chip Eggo. I put it in the
microwave. I didn't put it on a plate or
anything. I just put it inside the
microwave like on that glass thing. And
then I was like on my phone like waiting
for the timer to go off. And then I
smell smoke. And I was like, "Why does
it smell so burnt?" So I turned the
microwave off and open it, and boom! I
got hit with so much smoke. And then
Evelyn woke up.
>> She literally put my house on fire.
>> I was really scared.
>> She's trying to kill me.
>> Yeah.
>> And she ordered these Brandy Melville
They're so fat. It's like too much guys
Evelyn grinds her teeth in her sleep and
it's like literally the most disgusting
noise
ever.
>> I knew I grind my teeth but I didn't
think I grinded that bad.
>> It's like you're chewing on invisible
water. [snorts]
It's like you're trying to eat something
at first you were like
and I was like oh she must be dreaming
of eating and then she was like
She was like grinding the out of
her teeth and I was like oh my God
that's disgusting and it's like squeaky
it's like rubber you know when you
squeak rubber that's literally what it
sounded like
and she kept doing it like she stopped
and then she kept doing it stopped and
then did it stopped and then did it and
I was like bro I can't go to bed and
hear you grinding your teeth
next to me. It's disgusting.
>> Like midnight yeah you were up at
midnight? Yeah.
Dude I don't I didn't know I did that.
>> It's like it was dead silent and all of
a sudden here
>> [laughter]
>> I was like
uh
>> Ew.
>> I didn't know that's what grinding teeth
I thought you just like clenched really
hard.
>> I thought so too that's why I have TMJ
problems.
>> What's that?
>> Like
when you grind your teeth so much that
like your jaws kind of hurt.
>> What?
>> Mhm.
>> Mom has that too right?
>> Mhm. That's why people get Botox on the
jaws so that it like relaxes the
muscles.
But it's been a while since I got my
Botox so it's like hurting again.
>> Ew did she just kiss her nose?
>> Yeah.
What about it?
>> Oh.
>> She probably has like my lip gloss on
her forehead.
>> Ew ew
ew you went to kiss auntie you don't
know what's on her lips.
>> Diseases.
>> It's actually the opposite way.
>> Oh my gosh she just blew in my Ew her
breath stank. Your breath stank smell
like poo.
>> [laughter]
>> Smell like fishy poo.
Smells like an unwashed [laughter]
unwashed ass.
>> Ew, don't say that about my daughter.
>> [laughter]
>> Aw, Chai, you don't smell that bad.
>> Outfit for
second outing. Emily's wearing the same
thing.
Bye, Chai. I gave her
Greek yogurt and she is shoving her face
inside.
Chai, look up at me.
We look so cute.
This girl is on her damn phone this
entire day.
>> just on your phone, too.
>> What are you doing on your phone?
>> I'm researching where to shop.
>> Oh my god, this girl.
>> I want to go to Zadig and Voltaire.
>> Bro, I literally went to that store and
you were like, "Ew, I hate like this is
such a millennial store."
>> When?
>> Like a long time ago when we were
shopping.
>> Well, I was 12.
>> It's crazy. It's crazy how your little
sister is. They
>> [music]
>> They roast you, roast you, roast you
until they find out that you're so cool.
So, like
>> Actually, no. I think you used to
>> And like literally her outfit had to
tell me literally my clothes. Like
>> are mine.
>> You guys can't see it, but the camera
head is moving like and it's following
me.
>> It's right here or on the left on my
side. [music]
>> Um oh, we can just get off right here,
right?
>> Yeah, we can just get off right here.
>> We can get off here.
>> Okay, no problem.
>> Yeah, thank you so much.
Get off your phone.
>> You were just on your phone, too. The
hypocritical behavior is insane.
>> Guys, every time this camera is on,
Emily's always on her phone. Let's do a
>> Yeah, and every time the camera's off,
you're on the phone.
>> Update, I got my sunglass frame
um a little bit tightened. I can't tell
if it worked or not, but it does feel
slightly better. So, I guess every time
I go to a Chanel store, I'll just ask
them to tighten it every time.
But, um
they had very cute new
uh summer I mean fall fall winter bag,
but I personally didn't like them too
much, so didn't really get anything.
And they didn't really have any of the
bags that I wanted, so
I'll just do it online.
>> [music]
>> Why do you like these?
>> Um cuz they're like that.
They're atrocious.
They're so cute, and you can wear a
basic outfit when you wear these,
it dresses it up.
Like I actually
Some people don't get it, and you are
one of those people.
>> I love Esmeralda, but I don't like those
wedge sneakers.
>> Obviously, my dress doesn't go with
wedge sneakers, but
>> No, yes it does.
>> me height.
>> [music]
>> So cute.
>> It's low-key a vibe to have your camera
intentionally greasy, so I put my nose
oil. You guys can go ahead, thanks. And
it like gives off like dreamy vibes,
look.
Ew, this is disgusting.
>> I don't even Wait.
>> Think about it. She goes,
"Wait, you know that's kind of a vibe to
like make it kind of smudgy?"
>> [laughter]
>> Wait, can you take some pictures of me
with the thing on?
>> Wait, I want it without the nose grease.
[laughter]
>> Taking pictures all day long.
All day long.
The lighting is really good right now.
>> She's not like posing. Guys, that is
Esmeralda. The the entire time I was
trying on my shoes all I could hear in
my peripheral vision was Evelyn taking
creatures of her shoes, her face, her
jeans, everything next to me.
Like literally. I think she took like
500 photos inside the store. And I don't
like any of them. I've just her shoes.
She's like literally bringing her legs
on the couch. I was like
Evelyn slippers they deserve its own
special compliment. She got one
compliment by the sales assistant. I've
gotten compliments on my pants. And you
know what? I like these shoes.
And they deserve attention. I just feel
like I just never post them online.
My heart just dropped.
Tomorrow we're going back to Jersey.
Oh, she's taking pictures of her
ballet socks.
I was like, oh.
I turn around you're not there and guess
what she's doing.
Taking pictures. Is this even recording?
Oh yeah, it is. Hey, we're now in
Central Park.
It's going to smell like horse in
two seconds. I know, I hate it. They
need to stop riding horses here. It's
like animal abuse.
And like I feel so bad for the horses.
In this heat too. Like it's not okay.
Oh, we stayed at the Plaza. Do you guys
remember this? Where we got that
Didn't we get Oh wait, I was like
reading the menu it was like a $100
sundae. Yeah. My Guys, I need to get a
new laptop for college.
I've had the same one since my freshman
year and I don't know what laptop to
get.
Hi, thank you.
Enjoy. Thank you.
Yes, perfect.
>> [music]
>> Do you like the lemon meringue?
I've never tried the vanilla. You've
never tried the vanilla? We can try that
today then.
I usually only I used to only get the
lemon meringue one, but then I
discovered the vanilla.
Fluffy looking one is the vanilla. I
would only get the lemon meringue.
They have a chocolate cake, but the lava
cake is a different flavor.
Hi, this looks amazing. Wow.
And that's the tuna tartare.
So good. So good.
Okay, I know my camera's about to die,
so I have to show you real guys real
quick with this cake This cake is so
good. Try it.
The meringue No, no, no. This is the
vanilla cake.
I know, but the meringue on top. Oh,
yeah. This is so good. Isn't it so good?
It's like actually my favorite cake in
the world.
Good morning, you guys. It's been a
couple days, and Emily,
me, my mommy,
we're going to this clinic in New York
and getting a consultation.
For the longest time ever, I've really
been wanting to get Botox in my armpits
because apparently it helps with
decreasing the sweat glands or something
like that. And as you guys know, I sweat
a lot on my armpits. Like even if I'm
not nervous, even if I'm not even hot.
We're on
like Madison Avenue or something like
that, 5th Ave, and
my bladder is genuinely about to burst.
Like
it's insane.
Yes.
We're here.
Hi. No way. This stuff
>> [laughter]
>> I love this Wait, this place is so nice.
I'm actually obsessed.
>> I know, like the Miu Miu downstairs is
like
>> Yeah, literally terrible, terrible.
>> Like, the fact [laughter] that it's
right there.
>> Sit, get settled.
>> Oh my god.
>> Getting my Master of the Arts, guys.
It's been 2 years.
>> It was so easy, right?
>> Super easy, right?
>> Oh, hi.
>> You Yeah, basically you're going to lay
like that.
>> Oh my gosh, guys. This is so chic. Like,
this is very chic of you.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh my.
I separated it. No, I separated it cuz I
don't want you to I don't want the same
needle cuz it's not going to feel like
>> Well, your pits are numbed.
Do you feel your pits?
>> I can't really tell if my pits are numb
or not cuz I
>> You sweat it all off.
>> Oh my god, I'm so excited for this.
>> No, this is so good.
>> Wait, if this goes well on you, I want
it. Cuz I sweat so much, too.
>> we could do every 4 months. It's really
when you start feeling like you're
sweating like a lot.
>> Do a lot of people get this done? Oh,
really?
>> Especially models. Because like shooting
and
>> Ooh, that's smart.
>> I'm going to make noises. Just ignore
it. Do you want the boob?
>> No, it's okay.
I literally
>> Please, don't tell me that.
>> Got it. Got it.
>> They'll like do whatever, massage, do
gua sha.
But, yeah.
>> underarms
>> Guys, she finished.
>> [laughter]
>> When she was doing it, like half of the
up the upper armpit wasn't sweating in
the underarm.
>> [laughter]
>> You were really dripping.
>> It was like a pool of it, but it's okay.
>> Should we go to the laser room?
>> Yay! Guys, we're getting our lasers
done, our facials. So, I need to take
off my makeup.
>> Guys, just finished with my armpit, and
now we're at this laser room, and we're
going to get some skin treatments.
Because I have rosacea, they have some
laser that's good for rosacea,
specifically for it, and I never heard
of it before, so we're I'm going to get
that done today.
And I'm really excited because obviously
rosacea rosacea sucks.
>> This is my skin right now.
But, other than that, my face is pretty
good. It's been behaving really well.
>> My skin's actually gotten a lot better.
These are just acne scars, and then I
have just like
a scab right here, and most of these
it's like flat. Basically, it's just
like a little texture, it's just like
scarring.
>> Guys, this is our family bonding day.
>> Erica's doing her laser first.
>> It's called red light
red light um laser, so no downtime,
super easy, just
>> Hollywood glow.
Can't wait for that.
>> [laughter]
>> It's perfect.
>> I think these work.
It's like dual, I can see.
You hold this up to me, and then I'll
take it in.
Okay, perfect.
>> Why are we Why is everything so
>> We need to get some wipes everywhere.
>> Just for the reds, and then we're going
to switch.
>> Guys!
I'm so happy. We just finished with all
our lasers and skin treatments, and now
we're It's 4:00, guys. It's 4:00.
>> here for 4 hours.
>> We actually been here the entire day.
>> I know. Like, why did that take so long?
But, oh my gosh.
>> Oh, it's so hot.
>> That was the most luxury and the
most the best experience ever, guys.
>> Dr. Umberine Mahmood
And
what